Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Higher school pay urged by Reuther, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Housing program held inadequate, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Industry blamed for Reds in labor, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Jobless protest heard, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Jobless total up 584,000 in month, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Labor party plan of Quill rejected, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Labor policies and politics collide at the White House, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Labor secretary bids states end union shop curb, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: Labor unity step is taken by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Labor, business split on outlook, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 27: Local law sought to ban oil stoves, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 28: Mexican labor use protested by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 29: Michella front Reuther charges, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 30: Mitchell critical of curb on unions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 31: Mitchell's appeal is spurned by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: NLRB is assailed over 'free speech', Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 33: President pledges action on Taft Act to a silent CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: Rail workers unite with Quill's union, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 35: Reuther accuses GOP of 'talking', Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 36: Reuther asks US job aid in rise of automatic plants, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 37: Reuther attacks CIO disparagers, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 38: Reuther bids US aid Middle East, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 39: Reuther charges business rules US, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 40: Reuther charges inaction on jobs, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 41: Reuther holds economic report ignores inroads of robot jobs, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 42: Reuther letter ordering welfare fund clean up, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 43: Reuther outlines new deal-fair deal plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 44: Reuther says idle cost US 30 billion, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 45: Reuther sees US bled by idleness, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 46: Reuther sets CIO convention stage for attack on administration, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 47: Reuther showing fast start pays, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 48: Reuther tells French GOP is not President, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 49: Reuther wins Mexican friends for US, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 50: Reuther witness gives himself up, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 51: Ship union scores Republican party, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 52: State referee rules two local men fired because of union activities.., Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 53: State right-to-work statutes hit by Mitchell at CIO Parley, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 54: State taxes criticized, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 55: Steel CIO split may be postponed, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 56: Taft Law 'changes' are scored by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 57: Taft-Hartley Act repeal demanded in CIO vote, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 58: Text of the address by Secretary of Labor Mitchell at CIO convention, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 59: Union funds code outlined by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 60: Unions and Commissions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 61: Unions influence debated in Detroit, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 62: US loyalty setup challenged by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 63: CIO aide praises moral rearming, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 64: 200 at welfare Parley, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 65: Bethlehem, CIO to resume talks, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 66: Cartel bias hurt US aid, CIO say, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 67: CIO acts for labor unity ratifies ban on union raids, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 68: CIO again elects Reuther as Chief, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 69: CIO aide criticizes retail pay proposal, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 70: CIO and C of C back program to cut tariffs, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 71: CIO asks job aid in 'robot' plants, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 72: CIO asks labor to fight sales tax, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 73: CIO backs bill for new tanker, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 74: CIO calls Beck threat to unions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 75: CIO congress unit differ on economy, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 76: CIO convention, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 77: CIO convention scores Brownell, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 78: CIO denounces Eisenhower rule, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 79: CIO endorses Stevenson, says old guard runs GOP, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 80: CIO group assails Congress on record, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 81: CIO group reports campaign expense, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 82: CIO head warns of possible crash, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 83: CIO leader urges more aged benefits, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 84: CIO leaders in political huddle, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 85: CIO lists right and wrong votes, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 86: CIO publications defends plan of guaranteed wage, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 87: CIO reports given to jobless claimants halted then allowed, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 88: CIO rules few of welfare funds, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: CIO denies talk of union mergers, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: CIO deplores cut in maritime funds, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: CIO election tension mounts, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: CIO election tension threatens Schism ...Murray, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: CIO fears Congress will favor AFL, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: CIO fights Cole as housing Chief, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: CIO fights giving oil land to states, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: CIO give AFL terms for merger, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: CIO heads ponder Murray successor, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: CIO hits 'attacks' on Social Security, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: CIO is expected to act on merger, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: CIO leaders fail to agree on chief, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: CIO maps campaign for ballots in 1954, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: CIO may be readmit once-leftist unions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: CIO meets today in an air of strife, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: CIO negro groups visit Eisenhower, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: CIO opposes rise in briar pipe duty, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: CIO picks Riffe for Haywood post, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: CIO restores punch to organizing structure..., Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: CIO sets support of free union, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: CIO threatens to boycott administration, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: CIO to act on merger, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: CIO to approve no-raiding pact, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: CIO wants post with responsibility, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: CIO-Mexican group set, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: CIO's new leader, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: Clumsy' appeasing charged to Reuther, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: Cost-of-living index hints rift between Ike and CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 29: Depression likely in 1953, says CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 30: Dewey City steps assailed by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 31: Eisenhower leads fight on idleness, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 32: Eisenhower's talk criticized by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 33: Fire brings death to aged recluse, water flushes out secret wealth, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 34: Haywood death opens second place in CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 35: Inquiry asked by CIO on beating of aide, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 36: Is the CIO splitting apart?, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 37: J.V. Riffe elect. to high CIO post, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 38: Kroll says PAC delivered its vote, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 39: Labor industry peace holds in most areas, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 40: Labor law goals of Taft irk CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 41: Labor pioneer passes [Allan S. Haywood], Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 42: Leadership fight stalemates CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 43: Loss of Philip Murray leaves CIO a petty to factions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 44: Membership issue widens CIO split, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 45: Miss Lucy a very real legend, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 46: Murray funeral fills cathedral, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 47: Negro unit and CIO spur aim to set solidIke, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 48: Philip Murray, CIO Head dies on coast, leaders too stunned to predict successor, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 49: Program to lift controls spurred by CIO action, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 50: Red inquiries assailed, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 51: Reuther appeals for '5th' freedom, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 52: Reuther asks change in Taft-Hartley law, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 53: Reuther assails 'Tragedy' of public schools, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 54: Reuther asserts union blow was Taft Act goal, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 55: Reuther denies aim to go into politics, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 56: Reuther discards old index of prices, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 57: Reuther discards old pricing index, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 58: Reuther elected CIO head, Haywood is 2d in command, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 59: Reuther elected President of CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 60: Reuther given a year to establish..., Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 61: 2 Decca workers file complaint after discharge, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 62: 7 basic changes for Taft Act..., Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 63: Adjustments in labor field delayed by administration, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 64: Ahead for CIO - rough weather, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 65: Allan S. Haywood of CIO dies at 64, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 66: CIO accepts bid for unity Parley, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 67: CIO adds million to publicity funds, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 68: CIO again faces choice of leader, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 69: CIO aides see Eisenhower, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 70: CIO asks seven Taft-Hartley changes, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 71: CIO asks Truman to drop pay curbs, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 72: CIO backs trade to slash US aid, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 73: CIO deadlock remains, but Reuther gain cited, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 74: CIO delegates reported deadlocked on new chief, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 75: Reuther offering to Haywood', Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 76: Reuther predicts no rifts in CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 77: Reuther seen in lead to head CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 78: Reuther sees need of 2,000,000 jobs, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 79: Reuther will ask Truman to end pay control, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 80: Reuther's biggest job to hold CIO together, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 81: Reuther's verve marks meteoric rise to top in CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 82: Shipping and CIO split on alien bill, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 83: Stand-by controls approved by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 84: State dept. attacked by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 85: Steel allocation for ships scored, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 86: Steel union break denied by Reuther, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 87: Stevenson calls CIO to new era, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 88: Taft Law termed union growth bar, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 89: Taft-Hartley Act to stay, CIO feels, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 90: Tax exemption rise demanded by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 91: Three unions decide to merge, join CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 92: Tri-way CIO tilt looms with passing of Murray, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 93: US health plan urged by Reuther, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 94: White House faces dilemma in labor, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 95: White House held appeaser by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 96: White House seen as Reuther's goal, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 97: Who after Murray?, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: CIO's program for Latin America, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Negro in America today, 1955; Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Author: Alan Paton
  - Item 2: letter from James Carey, Secretary-Treasurer of CIO to Lewis Douglas, Southern Arizona Bank and Trust Building, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Author: Civil Rights Committee
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: CIO warns Commerce Department figures on unemployment do not tell full story on jobless situation, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee on Economic Policy
  - Item 2: Automation, 1955; Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: CIO's 10 point program to halt growing unemployment, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Conference on taxation, sponsored by the Committee on economic policy, Congress of industrial organizations, October 16, 1953, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Maintaining prosperity, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Statement before Senate Banking and Currency Committee on continuation of the R.F.C. and other proposals to aid small business, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Author: Emil Rieve
  - Item 7: Statement before the Joint Committee on the Economic Report on the economic report and proposals of the President, February 17, 1954, Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Resolution on economic policy, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Notes: Stapled to above item. 2 copies
  - Item 2: The Economic Outlook, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Notes: Marked 'confidential'
  - Item 3: Statement: submitted on behalf of the Congress of Industrial Organizations to President Harry S. Truman, December 10, 1951, Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Statement of Emil Rieve, Administrative Chairman, CIO Committee on Economic Policy to Congressional Joint Committee on the economic report, February 7, 1952, Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Federal income tax and the working man, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Author: Walter W. Heller
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Survey, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Standing Committee on Ethical Practices
  - Item 2: Report on proposed 'Employee Welfare Plan Disclosure Act', 1955; Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee on Ethical Practices.
  - Item 3: The CIO-AFL no-raiding agreement, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Homes for people, jobs for prosperity, plans for peace, 1949; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Homes for people, jobs for prosperity, plans for peace: a program to meet the inner and outer threats to democracy's survival, 1949; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther.
  - Item 3: Housing for America: statement, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Author: James G. Thimmes
  - Item 4: The church speaks out for labor, 1937; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Statement of Ben Fischer, CIO Housing..before the House Banking and Currency Committee on H.R. 7839, March 8, 1954, Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Author: Ben Fischer
  - Item 6: Good shelter for everyone, 1944; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Dept. of Education and Research
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Policies and objectives of regional development, 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Author: Anthony W. Smith
  - Item 2: Program, CIO Committee on Regional Development and Conservation: adopted Chicago, Illinois, August 9, 10, 11, 1949, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee on Regional Development and Conservation
  - Item 3: The foundations of prosperity, 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee on Regional Development and Conservation.
  - Item 4: The magnificent Columbia, C.V.A.: An overall plan for the Valley, 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the Resolutions Committee submitted to the Eighth Constitutional Convention of the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Constitutional Convention (1946: Atlantic City, N.J.)
  - Item 2: Supplementary Report of the Resolutions Committee submitted to the Eighth Constitutional Convention of the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: CIO Policy Statement for temporary disability insurance, 1950; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: CIO Policy Statement on improvement of State Health Agencies, 1950; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: CIO Policy Statement on voluntary prepaid medical plans, 1950; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: CIO Policy Statement on workmen's compensation, 1950; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Security for the people, Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Liberalizing unemployment compensation, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Author: A. J. Altmeyer
  - Item 7: Recommendations for amendments to State unemployment compensation laws, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee on Social Security.
  - Item 8: Report of the Committee on employer experience rating of the Interstate conference of employment security agencies, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Author: Interstate Conference on Employment Security Agencies. Committee on Employer experience Rating
  - Item 9: Summary of Employment Security activities, September 1940, Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Author: United States. Bureau of Employment Security. Research and Statistics Division
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of panels adopted by National CIO conference on Civil Rights, 1948; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Speaking for America - flyers, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee to Abolish Discrimination.
  - Item 3: All men are neighbors, 1944; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: C.I.O. wants F.E.P.C., 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: CIO head opposes seniority revision, 1945; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee to Abolish Discrimination
  - Item 6: comic book style pamphlet - "There are no master races!", 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Full employment and the negro worker, 1945; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: Willard S. Townsend
  - Item 8: letter, 1944; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: National CIO Committee to Abolish Discrimination: report of the director, adopted March 13, 1945, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: National CIO Committee to Abolish Discrimination: September, 1945, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Report of the National CIO Committee to Abolish Discrimination, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Report of the National CIO Committee to Abolish Discrimination, September 1945, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: The Negro comes of age in industry, 1943; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: Weaver, Robert Clifton, 1907-
  - Item 14: The Negro in 1944, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations. Political Action Committee
  - Item 15: The role of organized labor in education for racial understanding, 1944; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: George L-P Weaver
  - Item 16: There are things to do, 1943; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: Lillian Eugenia Smith
  - Item 17: To secure these rights, 1947; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Author: United States. President's Committee on Civil Rights
  - Item 18: What is the law, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Working and fighting together: regardless of race, creed, color or national origin, 1943; Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
- United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, Publication (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Communist domination of certain unions, 1951; Publication (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: CIO Committees recommend expulsion of four unions as Communist-dominated for immediate release, Wednesday, February 14, 1950, Publication (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Report of the, 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Author: Committee to Investigate Charges Against the Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers of America